simple1reading.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy ― Simple1Reading

#### Privacy Policy

**Simple1reading.com** is committed to respect the privacy rights of visitors. If you have any questions, please call toll-free 1-877-567-9468 or email us at [custservices@simple1reading.com](mailto:custservices@simple1reading.com)

Site Usage Statistics \- We collect general site usage statistics in order to improve our service. This data is not linked to personal identifiable information.

Order Information \- When placing an order we collect the following information:

  * Full name
  * Billing address
  * Shipping address
  * Email address
  * Credit card information.

This information is used to process your order, send you a receipt, and inform you of your order status. Your information will not be given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product.

We keep electronic safeguards to ensure the maximum security of your personal information. All orders placed on our site are protected by the highest level of encryption. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database, only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We also have reasonable procedures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control Credit card transactions are processed by a trusted third-party financial institution.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

We may email our clients about promotions, and offers. If you do not wish to receive this information, simply follow the instructions in each email or contact us at [custservices@simple1reading.com](mailto:custservices@simple1reading.com)

Please be aware that by using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Please do not ever send any credit card information by e- mail.
